I really don't
de verdad qué
know what to say talking about this man
me da conocida ya hablar de este hombre
but well he wants he insists he
pero bueno él quiere él insiste él
insists on giving the content to the
insiste en dar los contenidos a los
willow channels or so I have no choice I have
canales del sauce o así que no me queda
no choice he said it the
otra no me queda otra ya lo ha dicho el
other day every time he is taking things out
otro día cada vez que esté sacando cosas
of context and insulting us attacking us
de contexto e insultándonos atacándonos
and lying about us I feel
y mintiendo sobre nosotros yo me veo en
obliged to respond to him it's not
la obligación de responderle no es
because they want me to really it's not that
porque ellos quieran que yo de verdad no
I like to hit this
es que me guste darle palos a este
man or make him look ridiculous or anything like that I mean
hombre ni dejarlo en ridículo ni nada
I just encourage
por el estilo o sea yo simplemente animo
a touch up and you know if he doesn't dedicate
un retoque y ya sabéis si él no dedica
his twitter we dedicate ourselves to
su twitter nosotros nos dedicamos a
responding to him because
responderle porque las mentiras y las
we don't like lies and manipulations okay
manipulaciones es que no nos gustan vale
then we have to respond it turns out that he's
entonces tenemos que responde resulta
already giving well he's been
ser que ya en plan a ya está dando bueno
kicking like a drowning man for the week now
ya lleva la semana de hecho dando
and he doesn't know how to
patadas de ahogado y ya no sabe cómo
get out okay they saw what he did
salir vale fijaron lo que ha hecho esta
tonight that this is already not going to cut it
noche que esto ya es que no se corta
okay he took a piece of live to me
vale ha cogido un trozo de directo a mí
or do you remember one of the points of the
o os acordáis uno de los puntos del
green over that was manipulation no
green over que era la manipulación no
that he already proved me right the other day
que ya me dio la razón el otro día
when
cuando
when he manipulated the live of  4 hours
cuando manipuló el directo de 4 horas
adrián vale changing the title to make it
adrián vale cambiándole el título para
seem like the title was another
que pareciera que el título fuera otro
you can look at this click lie he is going
puedes mirar este clic mentira me lo va
to look at this click of a live stream of mine that he
a mirar este clic de un directo mío que
has cut to make it seem like I am
ha recortado para que parezca que yo
telling live and he confirmed what happened with the cat
cuento en directo y afirmó lo de la gata
and a whole white guy look at the clipping
y un blanco entero mira el recorte
call it put with this demo success what
llámalo poner con esta demo éxito lo que
I said to me he is confirming it
yo dije a mí lo está confirmando
to tell him that the rate that he has
para contarle que la la tasa que ha
told with a straight white guy reached is a
contado con un blanco hetero alcanzó es
lie you are going to deny it to me they have the
mentira me lo vas a negar tienen los
balls to deny me what to tell have you
huevos de negarme lo para contar habéis
seen the clipping or rather what I was
visto el recorte o sea lo que estaba
saying already and is it perhaps a lie that you
diciendo ya y es acaso es mentira que tú
without knowing me you answered
sin conocerme de nada me contestaste a
me and unknown people with a copy and
mí y a gente desconocida con un copia y
paste there he goes around spreading that the
pega ahí va por ahí difundiendo que la
cat had slept in the serious
gata se había acostado en el serio
and cuts the extract to make it seem
y recorta el extracto para que parezca
like I affirm it that I am the one who makes it public and on top of that at the end he leaves the little piece of perhaps it is a lie you are going to deny it to me freak out with the manipulation and on top of that he says here that he is throwing it in his face and
aquí que se lo está echando en cara y
says
dice
manipulative jone or what happens one
jone manipulador o lo que pasa que una
thing is that I  I told it privately and
cosa es que yo lo cuente en privado y
another thing is that they make it public, you
otra cosa es que lo hagan público yo tú
came to me to tell me so that I
viniste a mí a contármelo para que yo
would make a video spreading that
sacara un vídeo difundiendo esa
information shamelessly,
información sin vergüenza
I had the chat true disappear
tuve el chat verdad desaparecer
these people are not made to see
esta gente no está hecha a ver
these are many people did
está mucha gente
not say it removed it and I put it well you
no se dijo lo quitó y lo pongo bueno se
see the chat
ve el chat
true
verdad
review the chat
repasa el chat
now it always disappears I don't know why
ahora siempre desaparece no sé por qué
but I'm going to block everything blocked
pero voy a bloquear todo bloqueado
blocked what having blocked everything
bloqueado lo que haber bloqueado todo
blocked and I don't want it to disappear
bloqueado y no quiero que desaparezca
better
más vale
but anyway to everyone as I have already said to
pero bueno a todos como ya he dicho a
all the manipulations thanks the fox
todas las manipulaciones gracias the fox
sees how you get away with all the
nos vea como te las sacas a todas las
manipulations as I told you in the
manipulaciones como os dije en el
previous live I have given a gift
directo anterior yo he hecho un regalo
with the wine see okay so that every time you
con el vino ver vale para que cada vez
see a manipulation of Joan Plana you
que veáis una manipulación de joan plana
can respond to him with all the material
podáis responderle con todo el material
that they give him the green over okay to
que ellos le dan el green over vale a
this manipulation with which you can
esta manipulación con que le podéis
respond with these screenshots
responder con estas capturas de pantalla
where he makes public the private life of two others
donde él hace público la vida privada de
youtube.com you
otros dos youtube.com
already have material you have material so that
ya tenéis material teneis material para
during each tweet that Joan Plana puts he
durante cada tweet que ponga joan plana
starts to cry at each tweet he shuts his
se ponga a llorar a cada tweet le calle
mouth I have given you the material so that  do
la boca os he regalado el material para
it okay then apart I took it
que lo hagáis vale luego aparte cogí
says
dice
welcome to Rafa
bienvenido a rafa
if it's what the video says it doesn't say anything else
si es lo que dice el vídeo no dice otra
what I say in private is
cosa lo que yo diga en privado es
private
privado
Laurie thank you very much beautiful what I
laurie muchas gracias guapa lo que yo
say in private is private another thing is that he
diga en privado es privado otra cosa es
starts saying that about two people
que se ponga a decir eso de dos personas
well here when he says what I say
pues aquí cuando él dice lo que yo diga
in private is private you can hit him in the
en privado es privado le podéis dar en
mouth with this tweet for everyone to have
la boca con este tweet para todos tener
an answer for it clarify okay here you
una respuesta para ello aclara vale aquí
have help in plana complaining that
tenéis ayuda en plana quejándose de que
a whole white guy contrasts with his
un tío blanco entero contraste con el su
brother to tell him things the same as it is you don't have you
hermano para contarle cosas lo mismo que
have materials
así sea no tenéis tenéis materiales
now know this twitter that would put there you have
ahora saber este twitter que pondría ahí
a follower of his who is pathetic
estás una seguidora suya que es patética
this girl okay says she's a jurist
esta chica vale dice que ser jurista
but it seems to me that by law she understands
pero a mí me parece que de ley entiende
what what I know okay and she's
lo que lo que yo me sé vale y se está
complaining and this title retweets Joan
quejando y este título retuitea joan
Planas okay how bad are the followers
planas vale qué malos son los seguidores
of others
de los demás
how bad are the followers of
qué malos son los seguidores de los
others doing bullying well you can respond to this tweet
demás haciendo bullying pues a este tuit
with all these
le podéis responder con todas estas
screenshots that I gave away of
capturas que yo regalé de los seguidores
Joan Plana's followers bullying me
de joan plana haciéndome bulín a mí
defaming me slandering me  threatening me
difamándome calumniándome amenazándome
okay look threatening me okay
vale mira amenazándome ok
causing me it's worth it
ocasionando me vale
all it's worth it all to know
de todos vale de todo lo que para saber
this tweet
este tuit
but this is already a desperate attempt by
pero esto ya es patada de ahogado de
Lyon after yesterday I
lyon plana después de que ayer le
shut him up with
después de que ayer le calle la boca con
the invoices that he kept asking for there where are
las facturas que tanto él pedía hay
the invoices where is
dónde están las facturas dónde está en
the invoice why doesn't Carlos
la factura porque no enseña carlos
Salgado show what he spent the 14 thousand euros on
salgado en que se gastó los 14 mil euros
when I showed him okay well now he has no
cuando yo le enseñé vale pues ya no le
way if he's already started desperately
queda manera que si ya se ha puesto a
kicking himself saying that we have to
dar patadas de ahogado a decir que hay
see what he says the flight
que ver qué que dice que el vuelo le ha
cost him I don't know how much even comparing what he
costado no sé cuánto hasta comparando lo
asked for okay look at the trip here list one thousand
que pida vale mirar viaje aquí lista mil
five hundred euros two people round trip
quinientos euros dos personas ida y
okay and it says but if I do a
vuelta vale y dice pero si lo hago una
search here and it costs me 480 okay very
búsqueda aquí y me cuesta 480 vale muy
well one person and return for 432
bien una persona y de vuelta a 432
people it would be 860 but
personas serían 860 pero de todas
anyway the price of flights is very
maneras el precio de los vuelos es muy
relative okay the price of flights is
relativo vale el precio de los vuelos
very relative you can search for a flight
muy relativos tu puedes buscar un vuelo
or
o
from Madrid to Barcelona and it costs you
de madrid a barcelona y que te cueste
for tomorrow at 7 in the morning  70
para mañana a las 7 de la mañana 70
euros and now you look for it at 12 in the
euros y ahora lo busca para las 12 de la
morning and the new one costs you 500 euros, in
mañana y a la nueva te cuesta 500 euros
other words, simply by changing the time and
o sea simplemente cambiando la hora y el
day the price can vary by 10
día el precio puede variar por 10
and not only that, but the same flight at the
y ya no eso sino que el mismo vuelo a la
same time on the same day, maybe you
misma hora el mismo día a lo mejor lo
buy it now and you get one price and you
compras ahora y te sale un precio y lo
look for it in 10 minutes and it's
buscas dentro de 10 minutos y ha
changed, meaning he's kicking himself in the butt, he's already asking for
cambiado osea patada de ahogado ya pide
forgiveness, he's already made his head, he's already
perdón ya ha hecho la cabeza ya está
kicking himself in the butt, manipulating and
dando patadas de ahogado manipulando y
lying, victimizing you, cutting
mintiendo victimizando te recortando
clips to make them seem like they're supposed to, to put it
clip para que parezcan para para ponerla
in the mouth of others, words that we
en la boca de otras palabras que no
haven't said, you do
hemos dicho
n't know what to say anymore. Anyway,
ya no sabes qué decir de todas maneras
in the crowdfunding, it has been asked for,
en el crowdfunding se ha pedido hecho
but it is clarified that more is being asked for and that
pero se aclara que se pide de más y que
if there is any left over, it will be donated to the association, let
si sobra se va a donar a la asociación
the people decide,
que la gente decida
nobody is fooling anyone and go on,
nadie está engañando a nadie y va
nobody is fooling anyone, dude, get it
nadie está engañando a nadie tío
checked out because, well, your channel has already
háztelo mirar porque bueno tu canal ya
lost another thousand
ha vuelto a perder otros mil
subscribers, it seems totally logical to me,
suscriptores me parece totalmente lógico
okay, I, I wouldn't,
vale
I wouldn't be at all subscribed to a
yo no estaría para nada suscrito a un
channel like Jon Plano's, seriously, I wouldn't
canal como el de jon plano serio a ti no
support you and  nothing what's happening that she
te apoyaría y nada por lo que pasa que
's crying your videos have 13 thousand
está llorando tus vídeos tienen 13 mil
views 10,000 okay the end of your step has
visitas 10.000 vale el fin de tu step ha
made of trying to use antonio
hecho de intentar utilizar antonio
carrasco okay dirty with an
carrasco vale suciamente con una
interview that bidding year and a half 16
entrevista que licitación año y medio 16
thousand views this super manipulated video
mil visitas este vídeo súper manipulado
okay that he manipulated being title 2 and the
vale que manipulara ser título 2 y el
title by has also done if you see
título por ha hecho además si veis
manipulates the title okay but in addition he
manipula el título vale pero además lo
puts it with the same font with the same
pone con la misma fuente con el mismo
size hito so that it seems like the
tamaño hito para que parezca que el
real title of adriana's video this
título real del vídeo de adriana este
when in reality the headline here do not
cuando en realidad el titular aquí no
see no longer the dis the losses exceeded
ver no ya los dis las bajas superaron
like it is already finished you
like ya está acabado
are already finished and well
estás acabado ya y bueno
last night you were also helping because he
anoche también estuviste ayudando porque
also neutralized a video that I have already
también neutralizó un vídeo que ya he
said that here no I do not
dicho que aquí no
talk about now ends I mentioned or anything
no hablo de now termina mencioné ni nada
but it seems good to me that he made a
pero me parece bien que le haya hecho un
video because there is one thing that I did not say
vídeo porque hay una cosa que no dije
one thing that I did not say about an attack that
una cosa que no dije sobre un ataque que
made me joan very regrettable and they take out the
me hizo joan muy lamentable y los sacan
authors of the video
autores del vídeo
in it was esther
en fue esther
when I came to my flight cost 470 dollars
cuando vine a mi vuelo costó 470 dólares
and my father's only 90 my father
y el de mi padre sólo 90 mi padre lo
bought it a month in advance and  I
compro con un mes de antelación y yo lo
bought it the same day,
compré el mismo día
Senatel with the super that flights
la senatel con el super que los vuelos
are relative you can't say I'm not
somos relativos tú no puedes decir no
going to ask for 500 euros for the flight
voy a pedir 500 euros para el vuelo
when they don't even know the date,
cuando no saben ni siquiera la fecha
this thing that
esto que hizo
Julian Plana did in one of his
julián plana en una de sus patadas de
desperate attempts that he's been giving since I've
ahogado que lleva dando desde que lo
been [ __ ] him on the internet okay because I
estoy follando en internet vale porque
'm [ __ ] him or rather, no matter how
lo estoy follando o sea por mucho que
much I type now suddenly he
por mucho tecla ahora de repente me
made a video of me and they gave me the mouth and
hiciera un vídeo y me dieran la boca y
left me with a rag to take out a lot of
me dejara con un trapo de sacar a muchas
my garbage it doesn't matter now nothing will take away the
basuras mías da igual ya nada quitará la
night is that I gave it to him and it leaves him
noche es que yo le daba y que le deja
like what it leaves me my evil well it will
como lo que que me deja mi mal bueno lo
take it away how bad it is the voucher doesn't
quitará lo mal que es el vale no lo
take it away and giving his desperate attempts
quita y dando sus patadas de ahogado
as he saw that he couldn't do anything well he
como vio que no podía hacer nada pues él
would think let's see is that savinosa is
pensaría a ver es que a la savinosa le
affected by nothing that I tell him what can I
afecta nada de lo que le digo que puedo
do to make it hurt, what could it be
hacer para que le duela que pueda ser
for what the date has been, something went wrong with the
para que la fecha ha habido pasó mal con
naut airplay thing and he took it and
lo de naut airplay y ha cogido y ha
put the now you are worth it here and he didn't
metido aquí lo de now te vale y esto no
only do this on twitter what they don't
solamente lo hizo en twitter lo que no
know auto is that in my comments
saben auto es que en comentarios de mis
videos he also
vídeos también lo hizo o sea en
did it, that is, in the comments of my live stream like the turkey and he put comments on all the videos of all the live streams that I dedicated to him man man my friend my friend my friend Mario thanks churra for becoming a member again lie abandoned in the comments he commented on all the
en los comentarios él comentó en todos
rights and in all the live streams that I
los derechos y en todos los directos que
dedicated to him he commented oh what a shitty
le dediqué comentaba ay qué [__] de
video I don't know what I don't know how much and to the alca
vídeo no sé qué no sé cuánto y al alca
this day September 18th look what he
este día el 18 de septiembre fijaros lo
did is fix the twisted mind he
que hizo es fijar la mente retorcida
edited all the comments you can
editó todos los comentarios lo podéis
check it in the live streams okay they are
comprobar en los directos vale que están
summarized he went to edit all the
resumidos fue a editar todos los
comments to add this phrase that's what there is
comentarios para añadirle esta frase es
jabil thank him now tell me I will do it she
jabil dale las gracias a now tell me
will be very happy okay
haré va a estar muy contenta vale dando
implying that he is talking to an author
a entender que él se habla con un autor
who is not telling you things and that
que no te le está contando cosas y que
in the end he would be doing what
no te al final pues estuviera haciendo
the timer about helping to look
lo que el timer lo de ayudar a mirar
to report more by giving him data Miguel
para denuncia más dándole datos miguel
Gonzalez has made himself
gonzález se ha hecho
seen I do not put my hand in the fire
a ver yo no pongo la mano en el fuego
for anyone since what has happened to me
por nadie puesto lo que me ha pasado
but I sincerely God is
pero yo sinceramente dios nos está
speaking to us with this  turkey no way let's go
hablando con este pavo ni de coña vamos
no way he threatened that but look at what I'm
ni de coña amagó esa pero fijaros lo que
trying to do is like for me to get
lo que intento hacer es como para que yo
crazy if I ate my head and without
me raya si me comiera la cabeza y sin
docs the north is already talking to
docs ya el norte se está hablando con el
Joan Plana and the car is helping her
joan plana y el auto está ayudando a la
look and daily you all know what
mirar y diariamente todos sabes lo que
Joan Plana is going to happen to me if I keep
me va a ser joan plana si sigo
attacking him I'm going to see him here and there and I'm
atacándolo lo voy a ver y acá y allá y
going to stop saying things to him already in
le voy a dejar de decir cosas ya en
Plana because in the end he doesn't raise
plana porque al final no te levanta
things to you I'm going to notice the manipulation that I
cosas me a fijar la la manipulación que
did here
hice aquí
Javi thank her now I'll finish she's
javi darle las gracias a now terminaré
going to be very happy
va a estar muy contenta
and then I noticed for the saga telling him
y entonces noté por la saga diciéndole
look kid I've never spoken to you in my
mira chaval no he hablado contigo en la
[ __ ] life and on top of that you seem like [ __ ]
[__] vida y encima me parece [__]
scum that's it
escoria ya está
and let's see a few of the kicks
y vamos a ver un poco las patadas
Delgado has spent during this night
delgado ha gastado durante esta noche
okay
vale
and I say it to everyone you can
y la digo a todos a todos podéis
always answer everyone
contestarles siempre a todos
someone give him a tranquilizer and I
que alguien le dé un tranquilizante y
greet the neighbors on my behalf duck your
saludo a los vecinos de mi parte agacha
[ __ ] head once and for all because
de una [__] vez la [__] cabeza que
the plague won't be able to with me
la plaga
a tranquilizer because already Plana
un tranquilizante porque ya plana
and what's happening with my neighbors this is a
y qué pasa con mis vecinos esto es un
study  I have it and soundproofed in such a
estudio lo tengo y sonorizado de tal
way that it's not that the neighbors can't hear me, it's that they
forma que no es que no me escuchen los
can't hear me, that the
vecinos es que no me escuchan que los
children who have the room right next door,
niños que tienen el cuarto aquí al lado
free hugs, but your way is
abracitos gratis pero tu manera es
reassuring that if this is neither
tranquilizante de que si esto no es ni
more nor less than the same as how you
más ni menos que igual que como tú te
put yourself in the live that you deleted that I have
pones en el directo que borraste que
saved here, by the way, today you
tengo aquí guardado por cierto hoy el
want me to publish the live of the great
queréis que publique el directo del gran
plan that he deleted the four-
plan a que borró el directo de cuatro
hour live talking about a straight white guy
horas hablando sobre un tipo blanco
that I find very funny because they
hetero que me parece muy gracioso porque
help a straight white guy at the
ayudan planas a un tío blanco hetero al
moment of a white guy complete in the
momento de un tío blanco íntegras en el
video he dedicated a four-
vídeo le dedicó un directo de cuatro
hour live helping him but not me with the wine
horas ayudando pero a mí no con el vino
see me the guy has wanted to respond
ver a mí el tío lleva desea responder
but he has been responding to me
pero lleva una separan respondiéndome
every day he has already made three or four
todos los días ha hecho ya tres o cuatro
videos trying to manipulate he has already done
vídeo intentando manipular ha hecho ya
well every day you have dedicated
bueno todos los días tienes dedicado el
twitter why don't you do a
twitter porque no haces una reacción de
four-hour reaction john flat
cuatro horas john plana
go it's not worth it anymore because it's not the same
vaya ya no vale porque ya no es lo mismo
a week has gone by you have already been able to
ya pasa una semana ya te has podido
prepare I wanted you to do it at
preparar yo quería que tú lo hiciera en
the moment just like it exists
el momento igual que igual que existe
with HIV at the moment denying point
con vih al momento desmintiendo punto
by point only  you could not
por punto sólo podías no
but something about that current director
pero algo en ese director actual igual
is still calling me the kid from the
me está llamando el chavalito del el
whatsapp kid
chavalito del whatsapp
ah
ah
[Laughs] they
[Risas]
were sending me whatsapp
me mandaban whatsapp
javi is not harassing me seriously because
javi no me acosa en serio debido
sorry
disculpa
this is the dick well we continue here
esta es la [__] bueno seguimos aquí
says
dice
joan plana it's over gay no
joan plana se acabó gay no versión
planas version the end of johann planas
planas el final de johann planas
this dump called to the seo of
este vertedero llamados al seo de
youtube they must make tremendous dramas
youtube deben hacer tremendos dramas
when they argue with their partner or friends
cuando discuten con la pareja o amigos
without me answering the one that you answer
sin que yo responda la que tú responda
already like
ya en plan a
without you answering joan plana
sin que tú respondas joan plana
without you answering but if you've been answering all
sin que tú respondas pero si llevas toda
week if you've
la semana respondiendo
been answering all week
si llevas toda la semana respondiendo
without me answering I mean now he's
sin que yo responda o sea ahora está
playing the victim oh look they don't stop
haciéndose la víctima ay mira no paran
taking videos of me and I'm doing my own thing I don't
de sacarme vídeo y yo a mi bola que no
say anything but if you don't stop I the ones I
digo nada pero si no paras yo a los que
didn't answer were the cat from rodin
no te respondía eran la gata de rodin
girl and an hiv test and you wouldn't stop if they did
girl y un test de vih y tú no paraba si
n't stop and didn't stop and didn't stop
no paraban y no paraba y no paraba de
taking videos of taking tweets and know
sacarle vídeo de sacarle tweets y saber
what you said would be the clip
lo que tú dijiste que sería el clip
appropriate to answer this tweet, I have already
adecuado para responderte este tuit ya
said that with each tweet from Joan Plana
lo he dicho a cada tweet de joan plana
you have to answer her with the material that
tenéis que responderle con el material
I have given, I had done, I would study
que yo he dado había hecho estudiaría
that I would answer her with her clips telling her, are there
que responderle con sus clips diciéndole
quotas for criticism, are there quotas for criticizing, are there
hay cuotas acaso hay cuota para criticar
quotas for criticizing someone
acaso hay cuotas para criticar a alguien
unless you are a feminist, it doesn't help, that's what
a no ser que seas feminista no ayuda eso
you said, your own medicine,
es lo que tú dijiste tu propia medicina
well, and little more, little more, and publish a
bueno y poco más poco más y publica una
WhatsApp conversation, I don't know why and
conversación de whatsapp no sé por qué y
nothing, those of Quique are already waiting for your video,
nada los de quique ya esperando tu vídeo
we are delighted with your
estamos encantadísimos chávez de tu
video, Chavez, handsome, kiss
vídeo beso guapo